{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Jason _________ terribly tired last night. He had been working without a rest for over twelve hours.",
      "a": "had been",
      "b": "may be",
      "c": "must have been",
      "d": "used to be",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- We use must have (done) to say that you believe something is certain in the past.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Maggie ___ be in the classroom. I saw her in the restaurant two minutes ago.",
      "a": "shouldn't",
      "b": "mustn't",
      "c": "may not",
      "d": "can't",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Can: used to say that something is possible\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "One ought _________ for what one hasn't done.",
      "a": "to not be punished",
      "b": "not to be punished",
      "c": "not be punished",
      "d": "to not punished",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Ought to + Verb, but Ought not be",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's nearly six o'clock. Tracy ___ be here at any moment.",
      "a": "need",
      "b": "shall",
      "c": "might",
      "d": "should",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- Need: used when saying that someone should do something or has to do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Human beings ___ die without air or water.",
      "a": "have to",
      "b": "will",
      "c": "should",
      "d": "must",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Will: used to say what always happens in a particular situation or what is generally true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Must I take a bus to your house? \"No, you _________. It's just about a 10-minute walk from here.\"",
      "a": "don't have to",
      "b": "must not",
      "c": "don't need",
      "d": "shouldn't",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Need: used in negative sentences when saying that something is not necessary or not always true\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cleaner in the office ___ the truth.",
      "a": "didn't dare saying",
      "b": "dare not to say",
      "c": "did not dare to say",
      "d": "dare not saying",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Dare: To be brave enough to do something that is risky or that you are afraid to do\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ it be Jenny who took away the key?",
      "a": "Can",
      "b": "Could",
      "c": "Might",
      "d": "May",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Might: if something might happen or might be true, there is a possibility that it may happen or may be true, but you are not at all certain",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Its nearly 3:00 p.m. The beggar ___ be here at any moment.",
      "a": "need",
      "b": "must",
      "c": "can",
      "d": "should",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n-Should: used to say that you expect something to happen or be true\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you play basketball? \"I ___ play basketball.\"",
      "a": "am used to",
      "b": "am used for",
      "c": "used to",
      "d": "used of",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Used to + V \n- Be used to + V-ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "6",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}